JUAN GARCÍA

COMPUTER SCIENTIST

Born in Barcelona, 1994. I am passionate about science and technology, also interested in project management, business and communication. During recent years, I have taken part in numerous hackathons throughout Europe. I have also worked on projects of my own that you can check on GitHub or Devpost, linked on my website below. My specialisation is Artificial Intelligence.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE
POMPEU FABRA UNIVERSITY, BARCELONA | SEP 2013 - AUG 2017

MASTER'S DEGREE IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
UNIVERSITY OF ABERDEEN, ABERDEEN | SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

EXPERIENCE

DEVOPS ENGINEER

TRACKTIO | NOV 2015 - SEP 2016

- Full Stack software development in Node.js, Javascript, HTML and CSS
- Hardware development and deployment.
- Server management
- Database design and maintenance
- Big Data Back-End development for LORA
- 3D modeling for RTLS

HEAD OF THE DEVELOPMENT DEPARTMENT

GEOMAR | JUN 2017 - PRESENT

- Project Management
- Online Advertising and Marketing
- Full Stack software development in Node.js, Javascript, HTML and CSS
- Server Management

SKILLS

- Artificial Intelligence
- Software Development
- Back-End and Front-End Development
- Database Design
- Algorithm Design
- Python
- Java (Including Web Services)
- Network Security
- CUDA

- Advanced Math and Physics
- Signal Processing
- Probabilistic Models
- Genetic Algorithms
- Distributed Systems Design
- C/C++
- Node.js
- HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript
- Android
- Project Management

CONTACT

+34 672210152 ASTRAY53@GMAIL.COM JUANGMN.ME

LANGUAGES

• English: IELTS Proficiency

Spanish: Native

• Catalan: Native